<?xml version='1.0' ?> <rss version='2.0'> <channel> <title>News</title> <description>News - Latest Animal Births and Arrivals - Borth Zoo</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk</link><item> <title>Lynx kittens</title> <description>Only two days after her arrival the new lynx produced three kittens. &nbsp;The donating zoo did not realise that she was pregnant. &nbsp;We were surprised to see that she had produced kittens. &nbsp;We now have a lot of lynx. &nbsp;We will be careful how we introduce the lynx to each other. &nbsp...</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/lynx-kittens-2852.html</link> </item><item> <title>New Marmoset enclosure</title> <description>This family group is now quite large and, as their enclosure was quite small we decided to turn the large aviary into a monkey enclosure. &nbsp; It now has a new back wall, climbing apparatus and new planting. &nbsp;There is a tunnel connecting the two enclosures and the monkeys run throught the ...</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/new-marmoset-enclosure-2851.html</link> </item><item> <title>Coati</title> <description>The twin Coati are now out of their nestbox and they are learning to climb the trees. &nbsp;They started by climbing carefully and sometimes falling but after a couple of days they were racing about, playing and pushing each other. &nbsp;The male has accepted them and there have been no problems.</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/coati-2849.html</link> </item><item> <title>marmoset baby.</title> <description>The group of Marmosets by the kitchen have produced a single baby. &nbsp;This species usually have twins. &nbsp;Last time they had triplets. &nbsp;This single baby is quite large and can be seen carried by the father. &nbsp;The baby is passed to the mother for feeding.</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/marmoset-baby-2850.html</link> </item><item> <title>new lynx</title> <description>A young female Lynx was donated by Drayton Manor as she was surplus. &nbsp;She unloaded quietly and the same evening was observed talking to Nilly through the wire. &nbsp;There was no aggression. &nbsp;If they become friendly we will let them in together after a week or so. &nbsp;Nilly is very af...</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/new-lynx-2847.html</link> </item><item> <title>baby Emu</title> <description>The male Emu has hatched four babies. &nbsp;Some of his eggs remained unhatched. &nbsp;He tried to cover too many so some did not incubate successfully. &nbsp;He takes all four out onto the grass and has taught them to feed. &nbsp;The Emu are in the Zoo extension.</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/baby-emu-2848.html</link> </item><item> <title>Emu hatch!</title> <description>The male Emu is sitting on eggs in the house in the Zoo extension.&nbsp; He has fifteen eggs but we don't expect them all to hatch.&nbsp; The first chick was observed today.&nbsp; When the Emu started sitting he had seven eggs but the female continued to lay eggs by him over the next ten days and...</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/emu-hatch-2844.html</link> </item><item> <title>Kookaburra</title> <description>The female Kookaburra laid several clutches of eggs in the nestbox in 2014.&nbsp; In 2015 we moved them to a new enclosure and removed the nestbox so that she could rest and improve her condition.&nbsp; This year we have given them two nestboxes to provide choice and she is taking an interest in ...</description> <link>http://www.animalarium.co.uk/en/news_pages/kookaburra-2845.html</link> </item></channel> </rss>